- Hey, guys.
LEONARD & SHELDON: Hello.
(Penny:)It's a little loud.
(Howard:)No problem. Turning it down.
San Francisco, Lisbon, Halifax:
Voilà.
(Penny:)Okay, thanks.
(Leonard:)Hang on, hang on.
Do you not realize what we just did?
(Penny:)Yeah, you turned your stereo down
with your laptop.
(Sheldon:)No, we turned our stereo down by sending
a signal around the world via the Internet.
Oh. Get one of those
universal remotes at RadioShack.
(Penny:)They're really cheap.
(Leonard:)No. You don't get it.
(Leonard:)Howard, enable public access.
(Howard:)Public access enabled.
- Boy, that's terrific, but I'll see you.
- No, hang on.
[ALL GASP]
See?
(Howard:)No.
Someone in Sichuan Province, China...
(Sheldon:)...is using his computer
to turn our lights on and off.
(Penny:)Huh. Well, that's handy.
(Penny:)Um, here's a question. Why?
ALL:
Because we can.
Oh! They found the remote-control cars.
- But wait, wait, what's on top of them?
- Wireless webcams. Wave hello.
(Howard:)The monster truck
is out of Austin, Texas...
(Howard:)...and the blue Viper is being operated
from suburban Tel Aviv.
You may wanna put on slacks.
(Penny:)What?
Ew! Stop it. No. Leave me alone.
[DOOR SLAMS]
- Who's running the red Corvette?
- That would be me.